ICC Lombard is about to see its
results. Varun is ready to tell us
what is the market forecast. Varun, tell us, Deep,
we had expected the numbers to be good,
but
if you look at the internal numbers of ICC Prudential, they are a bit
weak. So
what happens in General Insurance of LTC? Our
estimate is that the net premium on offer will increase by 13.6%, it
can be around Rs 3942 crore. Profit will
increase by around 36%, it can be around Rs 475 crore. The
growth in premium in every segment has been quite
strong, so its impact will be seen.
If you look at it, the overall claim
ratio will decrease. So, it is a good
thing for the General Insurance company. It will decrease
from 72.1% to around 71%.
No doubt, there is a slight decrease in the expense ratio as well,
and
this will help the overlay company. In the
leader health segment,
Fox company has grown continuously, and
from there you will see more growth in communication, that is what
you will see coming.  If you have the power, then we are expecting a good
result,
we are running with ICC Lombard General Insurance,
so these are your
good numbers, that is what
Deep's internals are like,
because in ICC Lombard also the
profit in prevention was better than our estimate,
but the internals are quite weak, so let
me see what happens here, okay, so here are
your
upcoming numbers, we have
seen some action happening on both sides in insurance.